ladies and
Gentlemen The Life Insurance Company of
the year is sunlife of Canada
Philippines ladies and gentlemen to
accept the award please welcome Miss
ralina G maning CEO sunlife of Canada
Philippines Incorporated
good
evening I feel I know what it feels like
to be an Oscar
winner everything I thought I wanted to
say I forgotten but five years ago when
uh we were given our targets for
2015 we thought they were impossible to
achieve but we set about developing our
plans starting with the first financial
literacy advocacy in the
country where we are now is beyond
anything we could have imagined five
years ago and this award is a tremendous
affirmation that we have been on the
right
path this year as as was also mentioned
marks our 120th anniversary in the
country we have witnessed some of the
worst moments in our nation's history
and have also been part of its
success this award I hope sets us on the
next stage of growth for both our
industry and our
country and of course I would like I
can't uh end without uh saying thank you
our entire leadership team is here
they're the best team I've ever worked
with please give them a
hand and also thank you to my boss Kevin
strain and our regional colleagues are
also here they have us been of
tremendous support to us not least of
which is ensuring we have funding for
our initiatives so Kevin tomorrow you
will get another
request thank you very
much congratulations to sunlife of
Canada Philippines yes